Ashutosh Jasrotia

Web Developer

Solution-driven web developer adept at contributing to highly collaborative work environment and finding solutions. Proven experience developing consumer-focused websites using HTML, CSS, PHP and JavaScript. Good knowledge of the best practices for web design, user experience, and speed.

arshujasrotia@gmail.com

Paijnath, India

github.com/Ashu1864

. 08219049689

in linkedin.com/in/ashutosh-jasrotia-187726173

WORK EXPERIENCE

Drupal DeveloperCellworks.life

10/2021 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

- CSS, JS, Twig
- Problem Solving, Site Mapping and Content Manipulation
- Create Content Type and Paragraph Types
- Creating custom views and custom block
- Made custom modules

Drupal Developer mycareclinicaltrials.com

10/2021 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

- CSS, JS, Twig
- Problem Solving, Site Mapping and Content Manipulation
- Create Content Type and Paragraph Types
- Creating custom views and custom block
- Made custom modules

Web Scrapper & Drupal Developer faculty.alfaisal.edu

09/2022 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

- Used Beautiful soup to scrap Data from Google scholar
- CSS, JS, Twig
- Problem Solving, Site Mapping and Content Manipulation
- Create Content Type and Paragraph Types
- Creating custom views and custom block
- Made custom modules

Laravel Backend Developer lambandbeef.com

10/2021 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

- Made custom functionality of adding same data on multiple places
- Written custom PHP
- Deal with sql queries
- Create relationship between two table using code

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Bug Bounty (08/2020 - 10/2020)

 Worked as freelancer in bug bounty for TCS. THere were some security bugs in them through which any one access to there confidential informartion. So my work was to find that security bugs and resolve them. This all was done by using Python with machine learning and Data science

Impact of Covid-19 on Awareness of Personality Disorder and Depression (09/2022 - 10/2022)

 To analyze the correlation between the personality disorder/mental distress and covid-19.Plotting nation level distress frequency at different time intervals will show increase in frequency at the time of disctress. Using seaboard lib as mentioned in the requirement doc.

Fake News Detection with Machine Learning, using Python (08/2022 - 09/2022)

 There was a csv file that contains a lot of news haveing label fake or real we have to check whether the information provided is true and by how much accuracy percentage and also show the percentage of real or fake using graph.

ACHIEVEMENTS

I have done done a little task of finding the security bugs on the site of TCS. (08/2020 - 10/2020)

Finding security bugs and resolve them

SKILLS



CERTIFICATES

Full Stack Programming for Complete Beginners in Python

CSS Complete Course For Beginners

Beginner PHP and MySQL Tutorial

Elasticsearch Complete Tutorial With Python(Hands On)

Using Python to Interact with the Operating System

Technical Support Fundamentals

Crash Course on Python

WORK EXPERIENCE

React & firebase Developer

Gratisbooks.gailabs.com

08/2022 - 12/2022

Achievements/Tasks

- Made app using React App with firebase
- Created Login and Register functionality
- Created option of posting data
- Created functionality of like and comment

EDUCATION

Diploma

Government Polytechnic Kangra

08/2017 - 12/2021

Kangra, Himachal Pradesh